

MARCO BRUNETTI

ROLE SEARCHED: PROGRAMMER

PROFILE

10 years of experience in customs services. Hobbyist Unity programmer since 2017, actively programming prototypes ever since. Hobbyist musician since 2012, with skills in basic music theory, guitar, and singing. Currently searching a professional role in the game industry.

SKILLS

- Troubleshooting
- Long focus times
- Online research
- Quick learning of IT tools
- Advanced Excel
- Document creation
- Basic Photoshop
- Teamwork

CONTACT

+595 986 608 839

marco19-96@hotmail.com

Asunción, Paraguay

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NEGOCIOS Y SERVICIOS S.A. – GRUPO R.G. | 2017 – PRESENT

Customs Assistant, Asunción - Paraguay

Tasks:

- Reception and interpretation of customs documents
- Excel transcription and other office tools
- Management of national customs system SOFIA
- Management of IT tools

RG CUSTOMS SERVICES - GRUPO R.G. | 2015 - 2017

Accounting Assistant, Ciudad del Este - Paraguay

Tasks

- · Customs document management
- · Document registry and archiving
- Inventory loading
- Billing management

RG CUSTOMS SERVICES - GRUPO R.G. | 2012 - 2015

Assistant, Ciudad del Este - Paraguay

Tasks:

- Document transport
- Cash collections
- Wearhouse and inventory management
- · Communication in English with foreign suppliers

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Advanced

Portuguese: Basic

EDUCATION

2021 | Asunción - Paraguay

Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration

Universidad Adventista del Paraguay

PROJECTS

Current project:

Spectral:Demise Git

Old prototypes:

Unnamed FPS:

Git

Build

Mini Tanks:

Build

Crosscountry Racer:

Build